amdrewards.com 2019-12-28

# Privacy | AMD

  * Personal Information We Collect
  * Our Use of Your Information
  * Direct Marketing
  * Disclosure of Information
  * Security and Quality
  * Retention
  * Transfers
  * AMD’s Cookies Policy
  * Links to External Websites
  * Your Rights: Access to Your Information
  * Information for individuals located in the European Economic Area
  * Your California Privacy Rights
  * E-commerce partners
  * User Experience Program
  * Changes, Oversight and Questions

### Personal Information We Collect

We collect several kinds of information from you, depending on the AMD product, service or technology you use, including AMD operated websites, or information you provide to us on request.

 **Online collection:** We collect personal information from you when you register for a forum or to receive email communications, download products such as drivers, register or validate products with us, create a user name and password, provide feedback, send email inquiries, upload any content to AMD websites, including photos, or participate in another part of an AMD website. The information that we collect is set out on the relevant pages of the AMD website you visit and may include, for example, your name, email address, photo, postal address, postcode, country of residence, job title, daytime and/or mobile phone number, IP address and information about your workplace and the nature of your business. If you use an AMD website to apply for jobs at AMD, we will also collect information about your educational background and employment history and we will request your professional resume/CV. In general, you can visit AMD websites without revealing any information about yourself. However, where an AMD website requires you to register, if you choose not to register you may not be able to use its features to their fullest extent. For example, you will not be able to participate in forum discussions on that AMD website.

 **Offline collection:** We also collect personal information from you when you provide us with it at conferences, trade shows or similar events. Such personal information will typically consist of your business or personal contact details.

 **Collection from third parties:** In some cases, we obtain personal information from third party sources. These sources are public and non-public. Examples of public sources include trade directories or websites like LinkedIn. Examples of non-public sources include marketing companies from which we obtain marketing leads or event organizers where AMD is an exhibitor.

Back to top

### Our Use of Your Information

We use the personal information we collect about you for any of the following purposes: ****

  * providing, developing, improving and personalizing our products, services and technologies, including AMD websites;  
  * handling, and communicating with you about, purchases of AMD products and services you make through our e-commerce channel;
  * registering you for an AMD service or technology, including on the relevant AMD website;
  * providing you (subject to the ‘ _Direct marketing_ ’ section below) with updates, newsletters and/or marketing communications;
  * dealing with your inquiries and requests;
  * generating anonymous reports about use of AMD websites and their features;
  * allowing you to take part in AMD website features, competitions, campaigns, promotions or surveys;
  * providing you with online training on our products and services, including course materials, case studies and sales tools;
  * analyzing the data of people who use our products, services or technologies, including those who visit AMD websites to better understand how they interact with relevant AMD websites to enable us to understand and improve our service offerings (including customizing the content of our offerings), for example if you participate in AMD’s User Experience Program (subject to the ‘ _User Experience Program_ ’ section below);
  * producing anonymous or aggregated data and statistics that might help third parties develop our or their own products and service offerings; and
  * considering you for employment if you have provided personal information pursuant to an application for a job with AMD.

Back to top

### Direct Marketing

Where you consent, we use your personal information to provide you with marketing communications, including, but not limited to email communications or information about our products and services, new launches, promotions and special offers.

We send such communications by:

  * email;
  * SMS text message and/or any other form of electronic message;
  * push notifications; 
  * social network messages; and
  * any other medium which becomes relevant from time to time.

You can opt-out of receiving communications from AMD at any time by writing to the AMD Communication Preference Centre at [memberservices@amd-member.com](mailto:memberservices@amd-member.com) or by following the unsubscribe instructions set out in each of our communications to you.  However, we may still need to contact you in the event of a change to our Terms and Conditions, Privacy Policy, Cookies Policy or concerning an account you may have with us.

Back to top

### Disclosure of Information

Personal information is disclosed to the following parties:

  * to employees and independent contractors of AMD, analytic vendors, third party agents and other service providers and suppliers if the disclosure will enable that party to perform a business, professional, or technical support function for AMD or to perform a service that you have requested;
  * to our third-party reseller, and merchant of record, of AMD products that you purchase through our e-commerce channel;
  * to and between companies within the AMD group;
  * where you give us permission to disclose your personal information to third parties selected by us for marketing purposes;
  * if we are required to do so to comply with a legal requirement or request from a competent court, regulator or other authority;
  * where we deem it necessary, in our sole discretion, to protect our legal rights or property or the legal rights or property of an individual who registers with an AMD service or technology or any third party, or to prevent personal injury; and/or
  * in connection with a sale, merger, assignment, joint venture or other transfer or disposition of a portion or all of our assets or stock or our affiliated entities (including, without limitation, in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

We also disclose non-private, aggregate or otherwise non-personal information with third parties, including social media companies like Facebook and Twitter, and online advertising companies like Google, to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services for marketing purposes. You may opt-out of receiving marketing messages by using the opt-out mechanisms and links provided in each message. 

At this time, we do not track our users’ personal information over time and across third-party websites. We therefore do not respond to browser Do Not Track signals.

We take reasonable steps to ensure that any personal information about you that we pass to a third party will be held securely by that party and only be used for the purposes for which it was provided to them. Except as noted above, information we collect from AMD website visitors will not be shared with individuals or other companies unrelated to AMD, or that do not perform a business, professional or technical function for AMD.

Back to top

### Security and Quality

AMD is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect the personal information that you provide. We use a variety of advanced security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on secured computer servers that are located in controlled facilities. Additionally, when we transmit sensitive personal information over the internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol. Please help us to keep your personal information secure by not using an obvious login name or password and ensuring you do not divulge your password to any other person.

We do our best to maintain the accuracy of any personal information you supply to us. You can help AMD update and maintain the accuracy of any personal information you supply by notifying AMD of any changes to your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. In some parts of AMD websites, you may do this online by following the instructions on membership profile pages. You may also do this by contacting us at the address set out in the ‘ _Your rights_ ’ section of this Privacy Policy. Although we make every effort to create a secure environment for your personal information, we cannot guarantee the safety of any personal information you transmit to us online.

Back to top

### Retention

We will only retain your personal information for as long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes we collected it for, including for the purposes of satisfying any legal, regulatory, tax, accounting or reporting requirements. We may retain your personal information for a longer period in the event of a complaint or if we reasonably believe there is a prospect of litigation in respect to our relationship with you. We will actively review the personal information we hold and when there is no longer a customer, legal or business need for us to hold it, we will either delete it securely or in some cases anonymize it.  

Back to top

### Transfers

Where necessary, we may need to transfer your personal information to another country. These transfers can take place within the AMD group but also to selected third parties (as explained in the _‘Disclosure of information’_ section of this Privacy Policy). Such transfers take place to enable us to provide you with our products and services, for marketing purposes and for customer relationship management purposes. Countries that we transfer your personal information to may not have the same personal information protection standards as the country you live in. We will only make such transfers of your personal information internationally in compliance with applicable laws.

Back to top

### AMD’s Cookies Policy

AMD’s Cookies Policy is available for review here.

Back to top

### Links to External Websites

AMD’s services and technologies, including its websites, may contain links to other websites belonging to third parties. These websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices within any other website. You should be aware of this when you leave an AMD area, including our websites, and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of other websites.

Back to top

### Your Rights: Access to Your Information

You may have the right to request access to the personal information we hold about you and to have any inaccuracies corrected. Please address requests (with a return email address where possible) to:

AMD Communication Preference Centre  

Or by post to:  
AMD Web Services Team  
1 Commerce Valley Dr. East  
Markham, ON L3T 7X6  
Canada

If you are resident in the European Economic Area, please also read the _‘Information for individuals located in the European Economic Area’_ section of this Privacy Policy. You may have additional rights in relation to your personal information.

Back to top

### Information for individuals located in the European Economic Area

European Economic Area (“EEA”) data protection laws offer additional rights and protections for individuals located in the EEA. Further to the information set out at the _‘Access to your information’_ section of this Privacy Policy, the following additional information applies to you if you are located in the EEA:

  *  **Basis of processing:**  Where you give us your personal information to receive or use a product, service or technology from us, we process your personal information on the basis that such processing is necessary to give effect to the contract between us. Where you give us your personal information for any other reason, we process your personal information for our legitimate business purposes to respond to your request (for example, providing you with access to our websites or providing you with direct marketing that you have requested);
  *  **Personal information rights:**  In addition to your right to access personal information we hold about you (as set out at the ‘ _Access to your information_ ’ section of this Privacy Policy), you have the right to have your personal information rectified or erased, to object to its processing or to restrict access to it. You also have the right to lodge a complaint with your local data protection authority if you are unhappy with how we process your personal information. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to receive a copy of your personal information in a machine-readable format or to have your personal information sent to another company.
  *  **Transfers:**   Your personal information may need to be transferred to countries outside of the EEA for the reasons set out at the _‘Transfers’’_ section of this Privacy Policy. Jurisdictions to which your personal information may be exported include the USA, Canada, India and Hong Kong. Some countries do not offer the same level of protection for your personal information as exists within the EEA. We will only make such international transfers subject to legally required adequate safeguards being put in place to protect your personal information. For further information on or to receive a copy of the adequate safeguards we have adopted, please contact the [Communication Preference Centre](mailto:memberservices@amd-member.com).
  *  **Data Protection Officer (“DPO”):**  We have appointed a DPO in Germany who may be contacted for information relating to that jurisdiction at [privacy.germany@amd.com](mailto:privacy.germany@amd.com). If you have any other questions in relation to our processing of your personal information, please contact the [Communication Preference Centre](mailto:memberservices@amd-member.com).

Back to top

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits residents of the State of California to request from certain businesses with whom the California resident has an established business relationship a list of all third parties to which the business, during the immediately preceding calendar year, has disclosed certain personally identifiable information for direct marketing purposes. AMD does not share personal information about its consumers with any third parties for their own marketing purposes. We are required to respond to a customer request only once during any calendar year. To make such a request you should contact [memberservices@amd-member.com](mailto:memberservices@amd-member.com) or by post to AMD Web Services Team, 1 Commerce Valley Dr. East, Markham, ON L3T 7X6, Canada. In your request, please attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. Please be aware that not all information sharing is covered by the California Privacy Rights requirements and only information sharing that is covered will be included in our response.

Back to top

### E-commerce partners

AMD has partnered with a third party company, Digital River, as a reseller and merchant of record of our products and services online. Where you make a purchase through our e-commerce channel, your personal information will be shared between AMD and Digital River as necessary to fulfill your order and communicate with you about your order and as may be necessary to comply with our legal obligations. 

We encourage you to read Digital River’s privacy policy for information about how they process your personal information. You will be given an opportunity to review their privacy policy before you purchase an AMD product or service online.

Back to top

### User Experience Program

Participating in AMD’s User Experience Program allows you to share details of your experience with us so that we can continue to improve and develop our products, services and technologies. For more information about this program and how it affects your personal information, please read the information available at [AMD User Experience](https://www.amd.com/en/corporate/amd-user-experience).  

Back to top

### Changes, Oversight and Questions

AMD welcomes comments and questions on this Privacy Policy. We are dedicated to protecting your privacy and will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Due to the rapidly evolving changes on the internet, we may update this Privacy Policy. All revisions will be posted to the relevant AMD website. Regularly viewing this Privacy Policy ensures that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we will share it with third parties. If you do not agree to the changes, please do not continue to use the particular AMD website or AMD product or service through which you have provided us with your personal information.

Comments and questions regarding this Privacy Policy should be directed to the [Communication Preference Centre](mailto:memberservices@amd-member.com) _._

Back to top
